Division of Invertebrate Zoology Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- Staff and Affiliates, 1864-Present; Series VIII
  - Rudolf Freund Suriname Photographs. Rudy Freund Suriname Photographs., 005939
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 18 Slide 38: Paru Savannah & Fishing, 006430
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 19 Slide 22: Trinidad & Plane Home., 006431
- Specimen Photographs, 1864-Present; Series IX
  Photographs of specimens that cannot currently be attributed to cataloged specimens.
  - Cnidaria. Photographs of Cnidaria., 1864-Present; 001490
    - Cnidaria. A photograph of a Paramuricea. Unable to attribute it to a cataloged specimen at this time., 1864-Present; 001492
    - Cnidaria. A photograph of a Isophyllia. Unable to attribute it to a cataloged specimen at this time., 1864-Present; 001493
    - Cnidaria. A photograph of a Paramuricea. Unable to attribute it to a cataloged specimen at this time. See IZAR No. 1492 (same specimen)., 1864-Present; 001611
    - Cnidaria. 3 photographs of soft corals. Phots by J.M. Blake. Unable to attribute it to a cataloged specimen at this time., 1864-Present; 001613
    - Cnidaria. A photograph of Aglaophenia struthionides, determined by S.F. Clarke., 001527
    - Mussa dipsacea. Photograph of Mussa dipsacea., 005783
    - Sagartia leucolena. Photograph of Sagartia leucolena., 005782
  - Echinodermata. Photographs of Echinodermata., 1864-Present; 001491
    - Echinodermata. A photograph of Urasterias lincki =[Asterias stellionura]. Unable to atribute it to a cataloged specimen., 1864-Present; 001494
    - Echinodermata. A photograph of Ctenodiscus crsipatus. Unable to atribute it to a cataloged specimen., 1864-Present; 001495
    - Echinodermata. 3 photographs of Asteroidea. Unable to atribute it to a cataloged specimens., 1864-Present; 001612
  - Non-Invertebrate. Photographs of Non-Invertebrate specimens., 1864-Present; 001528
    - Non-Invertebrate. A photograph of Ambystoma mavortium. Collected from Lake Como, CO?. 14 Oct 1868., 1864-Present; 001529
  - Tunicata. Photographs of Tunicata., 1864-Present; 001557
    - Tunicata. Numerous photographs of Tunicata. Labeled by Verrill as "used by Van Name.", 1864-Present; 001558
- Miscellaneous Archives, 1864-Present; Series X
  Miscellaneous divisional archives.
  - Miscellaneous., 002802
    - Miscellaneous Archives. Specifications for display cases for the 3rd floor, South Room, Peabody Museum by A.E. Verrill., 09 Oct 1876; 001500
    - Miscellaneous Archives. Revised pecifications for display cases for the 3rd floor, west room of the Peabody Museum., 15 Jun 1876; 001498
    - Miscellaneous Archives. Miscellaneous payment and freight receipts and laboratory expenses. Included is an itemized list of expenses for S.I. Smith's trip to lake Superior., 1867-1887; 001630
    - Miscellaneous Archives. An account ledger for miscellaneous supplies., 1875-1877; 001625
    - Miscellaneous Archives. Specifications for laboratory cases for A.E. Verrill., 001497
    - Miscellaneous Archives. A list of furniture for two laboratories and private rooms., 001499
    - Miscellaneous Archives. A cardboard slide with a microscopically reduced page of the American Journal of Science on it., 002716
- Maps & Charts, 1864-Present; Series XI
  Divisional maps.
  - Atlantic Ocean. Maps & Charts of the Atlantic Ocean., 1864-Present; 001763
    - Atlantic Ocean. Pilot chart of the North Atlantic Ocean, Jul 1886; 001765
    - Atlantic Ocean. Pilot chart of the North Atlantic Ocean, May 1886; 001764
    - Atlantic Ocean. Pilot chart of the North Atlantic Ocean, Oct 1886; 001766
  - Europe. Maps of European locals., 1864-Present; 001761
    - Europe. A geologic map of Estonia. Map has separated into 9 squares, torn along the folds., 1864-Present; 001762
  - Miscellaneous., 1864-Present; 006519
    - Yale Natural Preserve Map. Map of Yale Natural Preserve and centroid coordinates., 006520
- Annual Reports, 1864-Present; Series XII
  Annual Reports.
  - Sheffield Scientific School. Annual reports for the Sheffield Scientific School., 1866-1886; 001768
    - Sheffield Scientific School. Treasurer's report for the Sheffield Scientific School fo 1917-1918., 01 Aug 1917 -31 Jul 1918; 001792
    - Sheffield Scientific School. Reprints of annual reports for the Sheffield Scientific School for the years of 1867, 1868, 1870, 1872, 1876, 1881, 1885, 1886., 1866-1886; 001769
  - Yale College Cabinet. Annual reports for the Yale College Cabinet., 1866; 001770
    - Yale College Cabinet. Reprint of an annual report for the Yale College Cabinet, undated but appears to be 1866., 001771
- Expeditions, 1864-Present; Series XIII
  Expedition related archives.
  - Remington-Leonard Expedition. Archives relating to the Remington-Leonard Expedition of 1930 (freshwater mollusks)., Aug 1930; 006523
    - Field Notes. Field Notes of the Remington-Leonard Expedition, August 15-30, 1930 to collect freshwater mollusks., 006524
  - Yale North India Expedition. Yale North India Expedition related archives., 1932; 001824
    - Yale North India Expedition. A binder of negatives and photographs of sites, people, etc., 1932; 001825
- Miscellaneous artwork and exhibit materials, 1864-Present; Series XIV
  Artwork unattributed to a particular artist or scientist.
  - Annelida. Miscellaneous artwork and exhibit material of Annelida., 1864-Present; 005762
    - Annelids. Miscellaneous artwork and exhibit material of annelids. Color illustration of Serpulid polychaete., 1864-Present; 005779
    - Annelids. Miscellaneous artwork and exhibit material of annelids. Color illustration of Nereis diversicolor, 1864-Present; 005780
    - Annelids. Miscellaneous artwork and exhibit material of annelids. Sepia illustration of Parapodia of Heteronereis., 1864-Present; 005781
  - Cnidaria. Miscellaneous artwork and exhibit material of Cnidaria., 1864-Present; 005758
    - Actiniarian. Depiction of living Actiniarian. Painting on slate., 005764
    - Actiniarian. Depiction of living Actiniarian. Painting on slate., 005766
    - Actiniarian. Depiction of living Actiniarian. Painting on slate., 005770
    - Metridium marginatum. Depiction of living Metridium marginatum. Painting on slate., 005773
    - Pavona. Depiction of living Pavona (Pavona aramata Verrill). Painting on slate., 005774
    - Sagartia acanellae. Depiction of living Sagartia acanellae. Painting on slate., 005771
    - Urticina crassicornis. Depiction of living Urticina crassicornis. Painting on slate., 005772
  - Crustacea. Miscellaneous artwork and exhibit material of Crustacea., 1864-Present; 005759
    - Crustaceans. Color illustration of Halimeda weed with the crab Huenia., 005775
  - Echinodermata. Miscellaneous artwork and exhibit material of Echinodermata., 1864-Present; 005760
  - Insecta and chelicerates. Miscellaneous artwork and exhibit material of Insecta and chelicerates., 1864-Present; 005761
    - Insecta and chelicerates. Color illustration of Graphocephala coccinea (Leaf-Hopper)., 005776
    - Insecta and chelicerates. Sepia illustration of Oligolophus spinosus (Daddy-long-legs)., 005777
    - Insecta and chelicerates. Sepia illustration of Galedodes dastugei (solpugid), 005778
- Digital Archives, Series XV
  Digital Archives that facilitate Collections Management
  - Miscellaneous Digital Images. Miscellaneous digital images created specifically for collection management purposes., 006541
    - Conus display drawer. Image of contents of Cornell drawer showing catalog numbers of each specimen, 006542
    - Conus display drawer. Image of contents of Cornell drawer., 006549
    - Echinoderm diversity. Image of contents of Cornell drawer showing catalog numbers of each specimen, 006547
    - Echinoderm diversity. Image of contents of Cornell drawer., 006548
    - Liguus display drawer. Image of contents of Cornell drawer., 006550